https://thevoiceoverartist.com/cookie-policy-us/

Cookie Policy (US)
This page was last changed on May 30, 2020, last checked on May 30, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://thevoiceoverartist.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settingsYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website.7. Placed cookiesDivi (Elegant Themes)
Usage
We use Divi (Elegant Themes) for website design.
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
et-pb-recent-items-colors
Retention
persistent
Function
Provide functions across pages
Automattic
Usage
We use Automattic for website development.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Automattic Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
tk_ai
Retention
session
Function
Store a unique user ID
Complianz
Usage
We use Complianz for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
complianz_policy_id
Retention
365 days
Function
Register accepted cookie policy ID
Name
Usage
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Fonts API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Google reCAPTCHA
Usage
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
rc::c
Retention
session
Function
Filter requests from bots
Name
Usage
We use Vimeo for video display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
__utmt_player
Retention
10 minutes
Function
Track audience reach
Name
Usage
We use YouTube for video display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
GPS
Retention
session
Function
Store location data
Functional
Usage
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
actppresence
Retention
1 year
Function
Manage ad display frequency
Name
Usage
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Purpose pending investigation
Name
_ga_*
Retention
2 years
Function
Miscellaneous
Usage
Function
8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Selling data to third partiesWe do not sell data to third parties11. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:The Voice Over Artist
Suite 288
4 Young Street
Neutral Bay
Australia
Website: https://thevoiceoverartist.com
Email: phil@thevoiceoverartist.com
Phone number: +61411114755This Cookie Policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on May 30, 2020
Search for:
About This Site This may be a good place to introduce yourself and your site or include some credits.
